zoomcasinos.com 2012-10-05

# PRIVACY POLICY | ZOOM CASINOS

As a matter of official corporate policy, Zoom Casinos is dedicated to protect privacy rights of its users to maximum extent of its powers. By browsing the pages of the website, you are accepting the terms of our policy as laid down in this document. Privacy policy is subject to revision and change by Zoom Casinos at any time, but user’s rights will not be reduced without prior notification and all changes will be communicated to members of the site.

**Personal information**

Zoom Casinos collects certain information about its visitors, regarding whether they are guests or registered members of the site. Types of information collected may include cookies, IP addresses and referral URL’s, type of browser and characteristics of computer system. Collected information is used to deliver services to our customers, measure website traffic statistics and improve our business model in other ways. In cases when required to do so by law enforcement agencies, Zoom Casinos may release your personal information. Personal information will not be released to third parties for commercial purposes without your explicit consent.

**Data security**

Data security is top priority at Zoom Casinos website, with technical and procedural measures of the highest level applied to all data transfers on Zoom Casinos website with the intention to protect our customers from identity theft and other forms of abuse. However, despite reasonable diligence the website is unable to guarantee its impregnability to cyber attacks and can’t be held responsible for any consequences of malicious actions of persons outside of direct control of the company. Users retain full responsibility for any sensitive information submitted to the website.

**Advertising**

Zoom Casinos may periodically send out circular e-mails or publications in order to inform its customers about the latest available services. Users will be explicitly asked to be added to the mailing lists and can remove their consent at any time. Third-party advertisements may be displayed on Zoom Casinos web pages that are not under control of the company. The advertisers could be using their own cookies to collect user information relevant for customization of the ads, in which case privacy policies of respective advertising networks would apply.

**Authentication and termination**

Users subject to this policy confirm they are older than 18 and that all data submitted is provided in good faith. Users will have access to any information retained by the company and can request the said information to be deleted.
